Oh my God, in this video I am going to
talk to you about a help plan
which is ICICI Lombard's help plan,
in this video I will
tell you everything about this product, coverage activation, so first of all let's
talk about that you can purchase Islam
which subscribes to 3456789,
if you subscribe to hospitalization, hospitalization
provides coverage for expenses incurred 30 days before hospitalization, you need to
subscribe to Ghrit, that is, discharge from the hospital,
and if you have taken Ayurveda Siddha Unani Homeopathy
treatment, then in that, if
you get admitted to the hospital, all the
medical expenses related to Venus and Gir organ donor, it provides you some slope, for that there are
conditions for it and which are set and till this much,
you have this
requirement of hospitalization, that is, treatment, if you
click on it from the hospital to home,
you get coverage in this year, the
child anger ambulance coverage is also
available to you in this plan, now two and 1%  1000 and
10,000 per event of emergency
hospitalization tele consultation if you
need war commendations for any health issues qualified medical practitioners
professional can do it for you so that if
you talk about the best and unlimited
then if you have the option then I had
specified in
Queenstown Pancreas and Paralysis of Laxmi
Phala requiring regular dala Ajay Jat then
you get it if your plan is above 10 lakhs then
you get it
subscribe this channel
you get it with this policy if your plan is up
to 5 lakhs then there is coverage of 2000 rupees per number
and if your plan is above 5 lakhs
then you get disability coverage of 3000 rupees per day
compassionate visit if any
English relative patient is hit his travel
expenses and between hospital to home and home to
hospital if there is more than that you get it up to 5
lakhs then share it and if you have taken time up to 5 lakhs then
share it and if you  If you have purchased from Rs. 5 lakhs
then if you are in a hospital with
nickel plated U for specialization then
if this hospitalization is for minimum 5 years then
you get
hospitalization cover of Rs. 1000 in plans up to Rs. 5 lakhs. For
plans above Rs. 5 lakhs you get hospitalization cover of Rs. 2000
and after that Rs. 3000.
Let's talk about favorable conditions and
benefits.
During hospitalization, you have been
launched in this scheme with the help of which you are
unable to do your work. To cover that,
if you are hospitalized for the first
year, then
you
get item coverage of contractor as well.
If you have taken a term of more than 5 years then
you also get coverage of tractor from time to time.
If you have
taken a term of more than 10 lakhs then you get worldwide
cover and also coverage if you have
left a term of more than Rs. 5 lakhs  So
you also get the option of super no claim bonus and
urgent coverage. It is hated
as the policy is given for a maximum of one
year for a medical practitioner. It is very important
that this diet nutrition consultant's
information of related to health care
service icon station diagnostic medical
equipments and comment it is the value
added services provided by Raghavendra
product Amazon Uber app and you must have understood
now let's talk about Next 9 Newsroom does
not share and subscribe over
hence you will not get their investment in this
experimental treatment is
not at all for cosmetic surgery so you
this recipe
is Snowden you will
not get institution coverage related to this treatment and treatment I
love you to accident sports activity
if you have undergone any dental treatment it does
not reduce if you are undergoing any dental
treatment due to accident
you have a waiting
period but if the
hospitalization reaches thousand then
you will not have to pay initial waiting period
and in case of hypertension diabetes
work condition fitting printed  It is possible but
if you have closed the settings
in PIMS first then this waiting period will not be applicable.
Now let's talk about it, it happens that the hospital
provides you and you
cannot even inform the person who subscribes to it. The grace period of
three years was
given by me on the plan, it does not happen
during that grace period, so
leave this plan, you get a grace period. Now let's
talk about that, why do you get
bonus for sharing the channel, this
cannot be the case and if
you have given my channel the
individual bonus, the thing is that if
you cancel it, your
Bharat Indian fee will be cancelled by the company as long as the
policy is valid. If you have
hidden any material thing from the company or
you have done some misinterpretation on which there is
Chandwara, then your policy will become null and void
and if you want to cancel it, then the
company will give you all the
necessary information so that you can pay the premium,
otherwise you must have
understood this very well.  You will have to
subscribe if you
want to change or if you find anything related to this then
you
can check Capital Chiku, we have given
links in the bio, you can contact us for their suggestions,
if you
want to know the premium then brother you can contact us,
please do not have tried to contact us
anytime, thank you so much